Oscar Hernandez Baute

Computer Engineer

(+53) 53841748 Cienfuegos, Cuba oscarhernandezbaute@gmail.com https://oscarhdezbaute.github.io/

SUMMARY Full stack .NET developer with over 12 years of experience in C# and .NET technologies & frameworks. With skills for teamwork & freelance with high job performance and years of overall industry experience. Experience in design, development and testing of software applications.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineer

University of Cienfuegos "Carlos Rafael Rodríguez" | 2003 - 2008, Cienfuegos, Cuba.

EXPERIENCE

CEDAL Inc - Industrial Automation

Full Stack .NET Developer | 2015 - Ongoing

- Leader of five full stack developers working in C# technology.
- Analysis of requirements with clients in the industrial, financial and health sectors.
- Design, development and testing of several applications back-end and front-end in the sectors mentioned above, using Asp.NET, C#, NET CORE, MVC, WebForms, Xamarin Forms, WinForms. EF, Nhibernate, API, RESTful Service.
- Front-end & back-end applications maintenance.
- Technical support to clients, experience with continuous integration and continuous delivery.
- Troubleshooting.

CEDAI Inc - Industrial Automation

Full Stack Developer | 2008 - 2015

- Front-end and back-end applications developer with Typescript, Javascript, HTML5. C#, Net Framework 3.5, 4.0 Asp.NET WebForms, MVC, Winforms, Razor, NHibernate, SQL Server.
- Data transport structures such as JSON, XML.
- Building layout with HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap.
- Desktop & web applications maintenance.
- Troubleshooting.

ABILITIES

C# | C++ | ASP.NET | NET CORE | MVC | Entity framework | NHibernate | ADO.NET | WebForms | WinForms | Xamarin Forms | REST | API | XML | XAML | HTML | JSON | Javascript | Boostrap | jQuery | CSS | SQL Server | Transact-SQL | Stored procedures | MySQL

RUP | UML | XP methodology | GIT

https://oscarhdezbaute.github.io/ PORTFOLIO

LANGUAGES Spanish: Native

English: B1 level